(gentle guitar music)
♪ There's a fire starting in my heart ♪
♪ Reaching a fever pitch ♪
♪ It's bringing me out the dark ♪
♪ Finally I can see you crystal clear ♪
♪ Go ahead and sell me out
and I'll lay your shit bare ♪
♪ See how I'll leave
with every piece of you ♪
♪ Don't underestimate the
things that I will do ♪
♪ There's a fire starting in my heart ♪
♪ Reaching a fever pitch and
it's bringing me out the dark ♪
♪ The scars of your love remind me of us ♪
♪ They keep me thinking
that we almost had it all ♪
♪ The scars of your love,
they leave me breathless ♪
♪ I can't help feeling ♪
♪ We could've had it all ♪
♪ Rolling in the deep ♪
♪ You had my heart inside of your hands ♪
♪ And you played it to the beat ♪
♪ Baby, I have no story to be told ♪
♪ But I've heard one on you ♪
♪ Now I'm gonna make your head burn ♪
♪ Think of me in the
depths of your despair ♪
♪ Make a home down there, as
mine sure won't be shared ♪
♪ The scars of your love remind me of us ♪
♪ They keep me thinking
that we almost had it all ♪
♪ The scars of your love ♪
♪ They leave me breathless ♪
♪ I can't help feeling ♪
♪ We could've had it all ♪
♪ Rolling in the deep ♪
♪ You had my heart inside of your hands ♪
♪ And you played it to the beat ♪
♪ We could've had it all ♪
♪ Rolling in the deep ♪
♪ You had my heart inside of your hand ♪
♪ But you played it with a beating ♪
♪ Throw your soul
through every open door ♪
♪ Count your blessings to
find what you look for ♪
♪ Turn my sorrow into treasured gold ♪
♪ You pay me back in kind and
reap just what you've sow ♪
♪ We could've had it all ♪
♪ It all, it all, it all ♪
♪ Rolling in the deep ♪
♪ You had my heart inside of your hands ♪
♪ And you played it to the beat ♪
♪ Could've had it all ♪
♪ Rolling in the deep ♪
♪ You had my heart inside of your hands ♪
♪ But you played it, you
played it, you played it ♪
♪ You played it to the beat ♪